One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Stella, it’s about time.
Mm, that it is.
I feel a little self-conscious
about being on a worldwide broadcast.
Well, then...
The break was so short,
my coffee hasn’t even cooled.
Where did I leave off?
You had only just introduced yourself.
Oh, that’s as far as I got?
The greatest brain in the world...
Punk Records.
It lives on, even after your death.
So, is this you,
Vegapunk?
What is death, truly?
Where do our ideas truly reside?
Our broadcast will
bring the world together, eventually.
It will mean knowing,
and the discomfort of being known.
Syrup Village
(Usopp's
Homeland)
East Blue
Whaaat?!
If it’s not at Kaya’s house,
then no one in the village has one!
Video Transponder Snails
are quite large, you know!
You can think of it like
caring for a gigantic pet!
I shall put on some tea, then.
Dr. Vegapunk played a huge role
as a leader in the world of medicine, too.
I know, right?
You fibber! Like you’d know that!
This is why you need to study,
Piiman, Ninjin!
Then you’d know, Dr. Vegapunk is...!
Starting in a few moments, sir!
Twin
Capes
Future
Land
Baldimore
Vegapunk's
Homeland
Was he born in this country?
Indeed. He is the pride of Baldimore.
Oh, the man who caused
the Nightmare of Baldimore?!
That was Franky.
He’s a ship now.
I haven’t seen you for decades, Vegapunk.
Birdie Kingdom
(Chopper's
Training
Grounds)
South Blue
Sounds like everyone’s talking about
the island where Raccoon Doggie is.
The father of modern science he may be,
but Vegapunk’s scientific expertise
helped to create a lot of weapons, too.
Pirate Island
"The Wasp's
Nest"
New World
Shut yer traps, ye lousy bums!
This Vega-whatever guy’s
got somethin’ to say to us!
Who now?!
You really think that’d get us to
let you off from cheatin’ earlier?
Get on with it already!
Can you hear me?
This is Vegapunk.
This is just an ordinary
Transponder Snail!
World! World!
Come in, World!
He didn’t just hide it...
he was planning to deceive us!
How dare you, Vegapunk?!
Come in, World!
Stella, the signal hijack
is one-way.
I know that!
Where is it broadcasting from?!
All right! Then, without further ado,
...let’s get on with the broadcast!
Yeah! Let’s go, let’s go!
What’s he kicking off?
What is it?
Go back to sleep.
Some important person has something to say.
It is not stopping!
Make haste, Mars!
Apologies!
Vegapunk must have taken
more serious precautions than we imagined...
...in ensuring the broadcast
would not be interrupted.
I do not know what he learned,
nor what he intends to divulge,
but York said that
he assumed Ohara’s research.
So he attempted to avoid
the same fate as Clover...
Were you hoping to avenge Ohara,
Vegapunk?!
I can hear...
...Bonney-chan’s voice,
crying out for my help!
Jewelry Bonney!
You shall never have the Marines’ arsenal!
Get back, Bonney!
What the hell is that?
Hold on!
Outta the way, Franky!
Sanji!
Only one man gets to
score points with Bonney-chan...
...and that’s me!
Don’t think for a second that
the elderly’ll get special treatment.
This is how pirates fight!
Sanji!
Stella!
What’s that?!
He was with the king of snipers...
Restrain that thing, Oimo!
You got it, Kashii!
Distortion Future!
Whuh?! She’s turned huge!
What is that?!
Jewelry Bonney?!
Huh?!
Giant-Like Future!
I have...
He’s started...
...committed two sins.
Therefore, whether I am
arrested or executed,
I shall program this message
to be broadcast...
...the very moment my heart stops.
What does he mean?!
Then doesn’t that mean
Vegapunk’s already dead?!
Whaaaa?! Wait a damn minute!
It was on the news just this morning
that the Straw Hats took him hostage...
What’s going on?!
Huh?! You’re kidding me, dammit!
Here we were, doing our damnedest to
force you out of the government!
Hey, whoa there!
You beat me to the punch!
If you broadcast to
the whole world like this,
you’re gonna ruin
the newspaper business!
Even so, I truly want you all
to understand this:
Whoever may have rendered
their judgement unto me,
I am not trying to convince you
that their intent is "evil".
I will not apply the labels of good and evil.
I know far too little about him...
...to be able to make that call.
Vegapunk!
What’s that thing?!
Go away!
So gross!
I have no time to waste
with the likes of you!
Stop, Chopper!
Huh?!
You are...!
That voice...
I see...
A bold hypothesis.
The Five Elders?!
Nico Robin, I presume?
Robin?
Eh?
The woman Akainu
allowed to slip through his fingers.
The man is far too soft.
Protect Robin!
Guard Point!
We’re keeping her safe, no matter what!
Get out of my way,
vile insects!
What I am about to tell you
is so unbelievable...
...that it might be met with laughter.
But all of you have the right to know the truth.
Think! Think!
Or I ain’t gonna be a Celestial Dragon!
I’s a Vegapunk, too!
Where would I hide it?!
No luck.
There are far too many
Transponder Snails in the lab.
There are no unique
Mental Waves among them.
Tell me! What will happen
if I destroy the power plant?
I would advise against it.
I do not mind the destruction of the Navy ships
and crew surrounding the island...
But we will never be able to recreate
the Mother Flame!
To make a long story short:
The world as we know it...
...is sinking into the sea.
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru